[
  {
    "question": "What is Thomas's sister name?",
    "answer": "Birdie",
    "points": 100,
    "num": "questionModal1"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the intent of the author?",
    "answer": "Historical fiction",
    "points": 100,
    "num": "questionModal2"
  },
  {
    "question": "What year is it in the book?",
    "answer": "1863",
    "points": 100,
    "num": "questionModal3"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why are the two sides fighting?",
    "answer": "To stop slavery",
    "points": 100,
    "num": "questionModal4"
  },
  {
    "question": "Henry reminds Thomas of who?",
    "answer": "Clem",
    "points": 200,
    "num": "questionModal5"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where is Gettysburg located?",
    "answer": "Pennsylvania",
    "points": 200,
    "num": "questionModal6"
  },
  {
    "question": "How old is Thomas?",
    "answer": "11",
    "points": 200,
    "num": "questionModal7"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Thomas follow while traveling?",
    "answer": "The North Star",
    "points": 200,
    "num": "questionModal8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who did Thomas and Birdie save?",
    "answer": "Henry",
    "points": 300,
    "num": "questionModal9"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did Thomas use as a weapon?",
    "answer": "A skunk",
    "points": 300,
    "num": "questionModal10"
  },
  {
    "question": "How did Thomas help the soldiers?",
    "answer": "Brought them weapons",
    "points": 300,
    "num": "questionModal11"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won the civil war?",
    "answer": "the Union Army",
    "points": 300,
    "num": "questionModal12"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who told who they should move?",
    "answer": "Henry told Thomas he should move",
    "points": 400,
    "num": "questionModal13"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Henry tell Thomas to move to?",
    "answer": "Virginia",
    "points": 400,
    "num": "questionModal14"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did they find Thomas?",
    "answer": "The forest",
    "points": 400,
    "num": "questionModal15"
  },
  {
    "question": "What happened to Birdie during the battle?",
    "answer": "She was kidnapped",
    "points": 400,
    "num": "questionModal16"
  },
  {
    "question": "What two places does Thomas feel at home?",
    "answer": "The camp site Regement and Virginia",
    "points": 500,
    "num": "questionModal17"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who did Henry meet at the Regement camp site",
    "answer": "Henry, Captain Campbell, Homer, Lester",
    "points": 500,
    "num": "questionModal18"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the president during the Civil War?",
    "answer": "Abraham Lincoln",
    "points": 500,
    "num": "questionModal19"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the authors name?",
    "answer": "Lauren Tarshis",
    "points": 500,
    "num": "questionModal20"
  }
]
